var myFlashcards = [     {question:"for trend in results OK even when full scope of claim not tested",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/atlas-powder-kollman-rinehart.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>kollman</b></span> </a>'},{question:"prima facie case, if rebutted, gotta start over",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/atlas-powder-kollman-rinehart.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>rinehart</b></span></a>'},{question:"combinations are fact specific",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/10/howard.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>howard v. detroit stoveworks</b></span></a>'},{question:"old BPAI case for 103",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/amgen-levengood.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>levengood</b></span></a>'},{question:"no per se rule contents and mode of operation of invention don't count, just that if disclosed structures are the same would have been obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/clay-dunn-innovention-toys-thibault.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>Thibault</b></span></a>'},{question:"for reference to teach away it must criticize, discredit or otherwise discourage...",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/depuy-spine-sirf.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>depuy spine</b></span></a>'},{question:"alternative method doesnt teach away",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/clay-dunn-innovention-toys-thibault.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Dunn</b></span></a>'},{question:"'needle in a haystack' obviousness of member of group of compounds",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/luvisi-nievelt.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>luvisi</b></span></a>'},{question:"combining teachings doesnt mean combining structures",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/luvisi-nievelt.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>nievelt</b></span></a>'},{question:"for not challenging official notice defaults to affirming examiner",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/ahlert-fox-grams-meyer.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>fox, ahlert</b></span></a>'},{question:"used for different purpose but still prima facie obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/landgraf-lintner-muchmore-serrano.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>lintner</b></span></a>'},{question:"commercial success must be tied to features of invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/leshin-superguide-syest-wyer.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>ayest</b></span></a>'},{question:"selection of material based on suitability is a design consideration any POSITA would know",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/leshin-superguide-syest-wyer.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>leshin</b></span></a>'},{question:"if embodiment falling within claim encompasses unexpected result then nonobvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/datamize-fisher-kao-ricoh.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>kao</b></span></a>'},{question:"teaching away requires being discouraged from following path",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/datamize-fisher-kao-ricoh.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>ricoh</b></span></a>'},{question:"change in shape of graphic doesnt affect method step",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/clinical-products-dailey-erlich.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>dailey</b></span></a>'},{question:"for preponderance of the evidence",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/caveney-oetiker.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>caveney and oetiker</b></span></a>'},{question:"possible choices of species among genus obvious if prior art provides direction",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/bilski-boehringer-corkill-manziere-mayo.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>pharmstem, merck, corkill, susi</b></span></a>'},{question:"sustaining multiple reference rejection but relying on only one OK",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/boyer-bush-celeritas-crish-kuhle.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>bush, boyer</b></span></a>'},{question:"elimination of a prior art feature along with its function is obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/boyer-bush-celeritas-crish-kuhle.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>thompson, kuhle</b></span></a>'},{question:"test for analogous art in 103 a. same field b. reasonable pertinent to problem. reasonable pertinent means would have commended itself to inventor considering problem",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/bigio-brana-clay-innovention-toys.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>innovention, bigio, clay</b></span></a>'},{question:"103 doesn't have to include everything from each reference",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/bowles-griver-papst-motoren.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>griver</b></span></a>'},{question:"if proposed modification makes prior art unsatisfactory for its purpose, not obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/amhil-asahiamerica-bell-and-howell.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>Tec Air</b></span></a>'},{question:"need nexus in declarations to prove non-obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/demaco-rosco.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>demaco</b></span></a>'},{question:"cant use applicants own disclosure against him/her",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/basell-katz-vogel.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>katz</b></span></a>'},{question:"failures of experimenters with no interest in succeeding given no weight",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/anchor-wall-deering-laryngeal-michalek.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>michalek, reid</b></span></a>'},{question:"prima facie case in combination needs reason to combine, which is a question of fact",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/allen-engg-boehringer-ims-jung-kinetic.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>jung, kinetic concepts</b></span></a>'},{question:"post-filing evidence may be used to demonstrate unexpected results.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/genetics-institute-mayhew.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>genetics institute</b></span></a>'},{question:"expert opinion, declarations only as good as facts supporting them",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/beattie-genentech-koito-perreira.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>perreria, beattie</b></span></a>'},{question:"examiner must consider declaration",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/alton-automotive-technologies-genentech.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>alton</b></span></a>'},{question:"POSITA must have reasonable expectation of success in light of prior art.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/amgen-kubin.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>amgen, kubin</b></span></a>'},{question:"requires that each of the prior art compositions be useful for the same pupose",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/kerkhoven.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>kerkhovan</b></span></a>'},{question:"strong prima facie case of obviousness cannot be overcome with weak objective indicia of nonobviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/otto-thibault-tokai.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>tokai</b></span></a>'},{question:"combining two embodiments disclosed next to each other is obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/boston-scientific-flo-healthcare.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>boston scientific</b></span></a>'},{question:"commesurate in scope with the claims does not mean testing every embodiment just adequate basis for support",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/advanced-cardiovascular-antor-media.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>kao</b></span></a>'},{question:"'integral' covers more than unitary or 'one-piece' construction",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/advanced-cardiovascular-antor-media.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>dike, advanced cardiovascular</b></span></a>'},{question:"prior art approaching claimed range may render obvious ranges without allegations of criticality",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/clearvalue.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>clearvalue</b></span></a>'},{question:"for admixing of compounds obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/rembrandt-tomlinson-wesslau.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>tomlinson</b></span></a>'},{question:"if applicant rebuts prima facie case, entire matter is to be reweighed",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/hedges-young.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>hedges, young</b></span></a>'},{question:"for obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/rembrandt-tomlinson-wesslau.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>wesslau</b></span></a>'},{question:"prior art recognition that a variable affects a property is enough to make it result-effective and optimum value for result-effective variable is within POSITA skill",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/appliedmaterials.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>applied materials</b></span></a>'},{question:"operative question is whether improvement is predictable use of prior art according to their established functions.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/ksr.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ksr</b></span></a>'},{question:"clear and convincing evidence for unexpected property",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/heyna-mcclain.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>heyna</b></span></a>'},{question:"conclusive evidence for new function",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/heyna-mcclain.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>mcclain</b></span></a>'},{question:"if omission of element includes ommission of its function, no invention if retained elements perform same function as before",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/chase-elevator-mclaughlin.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Chase Elevator</b></span></a>'},{question:"hindsight reasoning",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/chase-elevator-mclaughlin.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>McLaughlin</b></span></a>'},{question:"an inventor considering a hinge and latch mechanism for portable computers would naturally look to other similar references",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/icon-paulsen.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Icon</b></span></a>'},{question:"design choice only appropriate when applicant fails to say why would result in different function",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/chu-nash-olson.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>chu</b></span></a>'},{question:"precedent cannot establish facts",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/bicon-case-cortright-eaton-richdel.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>case</b></span></a>'},{question:"BRI cannot conflict with meaning of identical terms in patents from analogous art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/bicon-case-cortright-eaton-richdel.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>cortright</b></span></a>'},{question:"commercial success must be due to something not readily available",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/bicon-case-cortright-eaton-richdel.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>eaton, richdel</b></span></a>'},{question:"modification renders unsatisfactory for purpose inapplicable where operates on same principles as before",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/ratti-umbarger-union-oil-vas-cath.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>umbarger, ratti</b></span></a>'},{question:"references need not be capable of physical combination to show obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/andersen-etter-nievelt.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>etter, nievelt, andersen</b></span></a>'},{question:"examiner must explain how 'combining two embodiments next to each other in a prior art is obvious' pertains to particular case",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/arkley-boston-scientific.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>boston scientific scimed</b></span></a>'},{question:"ordinary skill to remove a feature not being used",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/larson-ntp-jasinski-gulack.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>larson</b></span></a>'},{question:"exploring promising new field where prior art just gives general guidance may be obvious but no bar to getting a patent",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/teva-ofarrell-mouttet-bush-cowles.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>teva, o'farrell</b></span></a>'},{question:"no legal significance whether primary or secondary reference",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/teva-ofarrell-mouttet-bush-cowles.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>mouttet, bush, cowles</b></span></a>'},{question:"claim can implicitly require method steps in particular order",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/baldwin-interactive-gift-mulder-gould.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>baldwin, interactive gift</b></span></a>'},{question:"invention not confined to particular form or mode described",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/donaldson-aristocrat-wms-lindberg-sasse.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>cont'l paper bag</b></span></a>'},{question:"making portable obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/donaldson-aristocrat-wms-lindberg-sasse.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>lindberg</b></span></a>'},{question:"motivation to modify prior art doesnt need to be same motivation applicant had",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/donaldson-carroll-valmont-johnston.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>alcon research, KSR</b></span></a>'},{question:"facts comstituting state of the art not amenable to official notice",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/eynde-ahlert-brown.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>eynde, ahlert</b></span></a>'},{question:"appellant must address facts upon which examiner rests obviousness rejection",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/fox-kunzmann.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>fox, kunzmann</b></span></a>'},{question:"ratti if modification requires changing basic principle of operation doesnt render obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/ipxl-schreiber-ratti.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ratti</b></span></a>'},{question:"USPTO has lesser burden of proof for obviousness in product by process claims",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/schreiber-altenpohl-fessmann-marosi.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>fressmann, marosi</b></span></a>'},{question:"prima facie case party with burden of proof points to evidence that if uncontroverted entitles it to prevail as a matter of law",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/saab-dunbar.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>saab</b></span></a>'},{question:"hindsight when at time invention made not obvious without benefit of disclosure",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/ratti.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ratti</b></span></a>'},{question:"single conveyor doesnt infringe claim element requiring two conveyors",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/cybersource-lantech.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>lantech</b></span></a>'},{question:"'consisting of' means only what is expressly set forth in claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/tronzo-cias-norian-gray.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>CIAS, norian, gray</b></span></a>'},{question:"when two known alternatives are interchangeable for same function, substituting one for the other still obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/aslanian-in-re-merck-keller-klosak.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>fout, siebentritt</b></span></a>'},{question:"cannot show nonobviousness by attacking references individually where rejection based on combination",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/aslanian-in-re-merck-keller-klosak.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>in re merck, keller</b></span></a>'},{question:"must show results inventor gets are obtained by invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/aslanian-in-re-merck-keller-klosak.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>klosak, mcclain</b></span></a>'},{question:"simultaneous advantages and disadvantages still wont obviate motivation to combine",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/medichem-mems-tech-norgren.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>medichem</b></span></a>'},{question:"hindsight inferred when specific principal within knowledge of POSITA leading to modification of prior art not explained",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/rouffet-texas-instruments.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>rouffet</b></span></a>'},{question:"combination requires that would have worked for intended purpose",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/biogen-seachange-depuy-spine.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>depuy spine</b></span></a>'},{question:"cannot draw on applicants invention as template for its own reconstruction",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/miles-labs-sensonics-gore-interconenct.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>sensonics, gore, interconnect</b></span></a>'},{question:"obviousness is sum of all teachings in the art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/railroad-dynamics-wright-brandstadter.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>kuderna, shuman</b></span></a>'},{question:"for commercial success need to show effort expended corresponding to length of need and others tried and failed",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/railroad-dynamics-wright-brandstadter.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>railroad dynamics</b></span></a>'},{question:"declarations fail if merely conclusory statements",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/railroad-dynamics-wright-brandstadter.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>wright, brandstadter</b></span></a>'},{question:"for long felt need must show art-recognized problem existed for long time without solution NOT failure of others",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/jella-dsl-newkirk.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>jella</b></span></a>'},{question:"obviousness test is what combined teachings would have suggested to POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/unigene-gpac-ruff.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>GPAC</b></span></a>'},{question:"equivalence in obviousness must be recognized by POSITA and not based on applicant's disclosure or mere fact",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/unigene-gpac-ruff.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ruff</b></span></a>'},{question:"post-KSR requires more than separate references showing each limitation",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/unigene-gpac-ruff.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>unigene</b></span></a>'},{question:"existence of licenses insufficient nexus to show commercial success to overcome obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/sibia.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>SIBIA</b></span></a>'},{question:"overlapping ranges obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/peterson-rose.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>peterson</b></span></a>'},{question:"change in size generally within POSITA level but not when component modified alone",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/peterson-rose.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>rose</b></span></a>'},{question:"computer doing what could be done manually unpatentable",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/king-ngai-nehls-kao.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>nehls</b></span></a>'},{question:"unexpected results must be established by factual evidence",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/klosak-ishizaka-peterson-geisler.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>geisler</b></span></a>'},{question:"person asserting unexpected results must show difference from closest prior art was unexpected",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/klosak-ishizaka-peterson-geisler.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>klosak, ishizaka</b></span></a>'},{question:"unexpected results must be commensurate with scope of the claims",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/klosak-ishizaka-peterson-geisler.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>peterson</b></span></a>'},{question:"after prima facie obviousness and rebuttal evidence submitted, all evidence considered anew",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/eli-lilly-piasecki-rinehart.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>eli lilly, piasecki</b></span></a>'},{question:"prima facie obviousness is legal conclusion, not fact. rebuttal evidence not evaluated against conclusion but against prior facts upon which conclusion is based",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/eli-lilly-piasecki-rinehart.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>rinehart</b></span></a>'},{question:"mere reversal of working parts not invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/einstein-gazda-global-tech.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>einstein, gazda</b></span></a>'},{question:"change in shape with no change in function obvious",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/dailey-gal.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>dailey</b></span></a>'},{question:"change in shape with no change in function obvious, however obvious design choice precluded when function different from prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/dailey-gal.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>dailey, gal</b></span></a>'},{question:"obvious design choice precluded when function different from prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/dailey-gal.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>gal</b></span></a>'},{question:"secondary considerations may not be sufficient to overcome strong showing of obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/07/pfizer-newell.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>pfizer, newell</b></span></a>'},{question:"long-felt need 1. widespread effort 2 skilled workers 3 knowledge of prior art 4 failed",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/07/toledo-allen.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>allen</b></span></a>'},{question:"for long-felt need those attempting to solve problem need knowledge of prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/07/toledo-allen.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>toledo</b></span></a>'},{question:"can't base 103 on speculative assumptions",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/07/steele-gorman-process-control-raytheon.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>steele</b></span></a>'}
     ];
